cmgdigital.com 2017-09-03

# Privacy Statement – Cox Media Group

### General:

Cox Media Group respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices. Questions regarding privacy issues should be directed to Cox Media Group at andy.mcdill@coxinc.com.

### The Types of Information We Collect:

Anonymous User Data . Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally to us. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to measure traffic within our site, and to tailor specific information to certain general classes of IP addresses.

Personally-Identifying Information . You do not have to disclose any personally-identifying information (such as your name or email address) to use most of the features of our website. The only personally-identifying information that Cox Media Group gathers through this website is information that you voluntarily provide to us. If you do provide us with your name, email address, phone number and/or other personally-identifying information when you use our website to ask a question or request information (such as through the Cox Career Network Help Form), we may use your personally-identifying information to send you a response and we may keep a record of your request or inquiry. If you use our website to direct an inquiry or request to one of our affiliates, we will forward your request and related personally-identifying information to the appropriate affiliate so that our affiliate can respond to your inquiry. Our affiliates’ use of the personally-identifying information collected through this website will be governed by this privacy policy.

### Our Use of Personally-Identifying Information:

We will not disclose personally-identifying information collected through our website to third parties except as provided in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to release personally-identifying information about our website visitors when we believe that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with law or to protect the safety or property of Cox Media Group, visitors to our site, the public, our affiliates and/or our personnel. We also reserve the right to disclose personally-identifying information about our website visitors to third-party contractors we engage to assist us with the operation of our website or other aspects of our business when our contractors need access to such information to perform the services we request. In the unlikely event that Cox Media Group merges with another entity or otherwise transfers substantially all of its assets to another entity, information collected from our website visitors would be among the transferred assets.

### Links to Other Websites:

Our website may include links to other websites operated by third parties whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website through our website, any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any third-party website you access through our site.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy:

A final note: The Web is an evolving medium. We may update our Privacy Policy at any time. By visiting our site, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over our privacy practices, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our  [Visitor Agreement.](http://www.coxmediagroup.com/visitor-agreement/)
